<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>UbuCon Asia 2022</title>
    <link>https://2022.ubucon.asia/</link>
    <description>Recent content on UbuCon Asia 2022</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 21 Jul 2022 22:00:00 +0900</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://2022.ubucon.asia/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>UbuCon Asia 2022 - Nov 26-27 Seoul, South Korea</title>
      <link>https://2022.ubucon.asia/news/2022-07-21-ubucon-asia-2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jul 2022 22:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://2022.ubucon.asia/news/2022-07-21-ubucon-asia-2022/</guid>
      <description>Introducing the first In-person UbuCon in Asia, UbuCon Asia 2022
With venue sponsorship from NIPA(National IT Industry Promotion Agency),
The event will be hold at Nuritkum Square, Seoul, South Korea. Event dates will be November 26-27
We&amp;rsquo;re planning event with 3 tracks simultaneously. Talk(or Lecture) track, Workshop(or Hands on Lab) track, and BoF/Short lecture track. More details will be available on this website and social media. Save the date, and see you in Seoul!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>UbuCon Asia 2022 will be on Seoul, South Korea</title>
      <link>https://2022.ubucon.asia/news/2022-06-21-ubucon-asia-2022-in-korea/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Jun 2022 23:30:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://2022.ubucon.asia/news/2022-06-21-ubucon-asia-2022-in-korea/</guid>
      <description>The UbuCon Asia 2022 will be on Seoul, South Korea. It will be an in-person and online hybrid format.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Automating boring and repetitive UbuCon Asia video and subtitle stuffs 
</title>
      <link>https://2022.ubucon.asia/sessions/automating_boring_and_repetitive_ubucon_asia_video_and_subtitle_stuffs/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Sep 2021 14:15:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://2022.ubucon.asia/sessions/automating_boring_and_repetitive_ubucon_asia_video_and_subtitle_stuffs/</guid>
      <description>Whether it&amp;rsquo;s online or offline event, There&amp;rsquo;s always boring and repetitive jobs for event organizers and volunteers. Putting cover on session videos and making subtitle for videos are part of them. UbuCon Asia team, is no exception. But like you and other ordinary people, our organizers also have their own job and busy with that usually. As it&amp;rsquo;s first event we don&amp;rsquo;t even know if we can gather enough volunteers or gain sponsorship to hire some workers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About UbuCon Asia 2022</title>
      <link>https://2022.ubucon.asia/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://2022.ubucon.asia/about/</guid>
      <description>UbuCon Asia is an event organized by Ubuntu Communities in Asia. It&amp;rsquo;s for everyone who involved with or interested in Ubuntu, Linux and other Free and Open source technologies. It is also a place for Ubuntu people from Asia to connect, learn, and share their knowlegdes each other.
UbuCon Asia 2022 will be the first In-person UbuCon Asia event. And It will be hold at Nuritkum Square (Nuri Dream Square) in Seoul, South Korea.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Become a sponsor</title>
      <link>https://2022.ubucon.asia/sponsors/become-a-sponsor/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://2022.ubucon.asia/sponsors/become-a-sponsor/</guid>
      <description>Thank you for your interest in Ubuntu and Ubucon Asia.
As a non-profit and community organized event, Even Ubucon Asia 2021 is fully virtual event, We still need support from sponsors to make the event happen.
By becoming one of our sponsors, you are directly contributing to research and development of Ubuntu and Open Source Software, and also making Open Source Community more active and sustainable.
Your contribution makes it possible for us to bring a large number of Ubuntu users and contributors across Asia to connect, interact, help and learn together.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>National IT Industry Promotion Agency of Korea</title>
      <link>https://2022.ubucon.asia/sponsors/nipa-kr/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://2022.ubucon.asia/sponsors/nipa-kr/</guid>
      <description>OpenUP - Open source software promotion organization at NIPA We are an institution that strengthens open source SW development capabilities and helps domestic IT and industries develop in various ways.
NIPA - National IT Industry Promotion Agency of Korea NIPA devotes itself to reinforcing the competitiveness of the ICT industry and contributes to the economic growth through the efficient support and laying the groundwork for the industrial technology promotion.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
